

Muhammad Moeez Ashfaq

Electrical Engineer (Power)

A dynamic and goal oriented individual, looking forward to build a career to utilize the knowledge acquired during studies in a true work environment and obtain greater experience through practice, who possesses good interpersonal, leadership, business development, human resource, and project management skills.

- ≥ moeezashfaq100@gmail.com
- House No. CB 271, lane#03, street#8, rashid minhas road, Lalazar, Wahcantt, Pakistan
- in linkedin.com/in/moeez-ashfaq-b84b07177

03414184863

SKILLS

26 December, 1999

f facebook.com/profile.php?id=100044159824948

Conflict Resolutions

Basic Leadership and Management Skills

Communication and Inter-personal Skill

MS Word - MS Power point -MS Excel

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Electrical Engineering University of Engineering and Technology Taxila

10/2017 - 09/2021

GPA: 3.11 Percentage: 76%

Courses

- Linear Circuit Analysis
- Communication Systems
- Power Distribute & Utilize
- High Voltage

- GFA. S. IT Fercentage. 10%
- Electrical Machines
- Linear Control System
- Power TransmissionPower Electronics

Pre Engineering-(HSSC)

F.G Degree College For Men, Wahcantt

08/2015 - 08/2017 Marks: 920/1100 Percentage: 84%

Matric-(SSC)

The Educators, Wah Campus, The Mall, Wahcantt

07/2013 - 07/2015 Marks: 908/1050 Percentage: 86%

PROJECTS

Problem-solving

FYP " Dual Axis Solar Panel with solar energy monitoring"

High Voltage Capacitor

Mobile Charger

Inverter

C02 concentration in air project using Arduino

Simulation of medium length transmission line model using MATLAB

Electric Braking by plugging method

Design of Marx Impulse generator

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship

Pakistan Telecommunication Company Limited

08/2020 - 10/2020

We learned about what services PTCL is offering? What are their future plans? What is GPON? How to make best out of internship? etc

General Member

Student Branch IEEE, UET Taxila

06/2018 - 06/2019

CERTIFICATES

MS Office Word 2016 Specialist (12/2020 - Present)

Specialist MS Power point 2016 (12/2020 - Present)

LANGUAGES

Urdu Engli

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

Punjabi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

